https://www.newformtools.com/privacy-policy/

Stratford, Ontario, Canada
Ship-To Address Port Huron, Michigan, U.S.A
World-Wide Partnerships
519-272-0921
Home (current)
Contact us
Your blades may not be ready to be replaced after all! Learn more about our re-sharpening services.
Privacy Policy
LAST UPDATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY – October 10th, 2018BEFORE USING OUR SITE, PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.This Privacy Policy is applicable to New-Form Tools Ltd. and sets out our policy on the gathering and use of information on this site. New-Form Tools is committed to providing a safe web site for visitors of all ages and has implemented this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. New-Form Tools complies with Canadian Federal and Provincial privacy laws and regulations including the Personal Information and Electronic Documents Act.There may be links from our Site to other web sites; note that this Privacy Policy applies only to our Site and not to web sites of other companies or organizations to which our Site may be linked. You must check on any linked sites for the privacy policy that applies to that site and/or make any necessary inquiries in respect of that privacy policy with the operator of the linked site. These links to third party websites are provided as a convenience and are for informational purposes only. New-Form Tools does not endorse, and is not responsible for, these linked websites.Although you are not required to register to access our Site, you may be asked to provide us with personal information when you visit certain sections of our Site. Your use of our Site signifies your acknowledgement and consent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not continue to use our Site. Your continued use of the Site signifies your acceptance of these terms and any changes in effect at the time of use.COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONPersonal Information is information about you that identifies you as an individual, for example, your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number.We collect information that you voluntarily provide to us through responses to surveys, search functions, questionnaires, feedback, résumé forms and the like. We may also ask you to provide additional information such as your e-mail address if you want to obtain additional services, information, quotes, participate in a contest or to resolve complaints or concerns.HOW DOES NEW-FORM TOOLS USE INFORMATION GATHERED ABOUT ONLINE VISITORS?Before forwarding us any personal information, please be advised that any information gathered on our Site may be used in the aggregate for research and development relating to our Site and/or for future site development and, if you ask us to, to send you promotional materials. In particular, we may use information gathered about you for the following purposes: to monitor interest in our range of products and to assist us to tailor the content of our Site to your needs by collecting information about your preferences through tracking of patterns page views on our Sites; to create a profile relating to you in order to show you the content that might be of interest to you and to display the content according to your preferences; and, in circumstances where you have indicated that you wish to receive additional information, to send you information about us and promotional material about our products together with details of any offers we may have available from time to time.DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATIONNew-Form Tools will not disclose personal information that you provide on its Site to any third parties other than to a company agent except: i) in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, or ii) to comply with legal requirements such as a law, regulation, warrant, subpoena or court order, and/or iii) if you are reporting an adverse event/side effect, in which case the company may be required to disclose such information to bodies such as, but not limited to, Canadian and/or international regulatory authorities. Please note that any of these disclosures may involve the storage or processing of personal information outside of Canada and may therefore be subject to different privacy laws than those applicable in Canada, including laws that require the disclosure of personal information to governmental authorities under circumstances that are different than those that apply in Canada.COOKIESNew-Form Tools, in common with many web site operators, may use standard technology called "cookies" on its Site. Cookies are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit a particular web site. You can disable cookies by turning them off in your browser; however, some areas of the Site may not function properly if you do so.PROTECTION OF INFORMATION:Our Commitment to SecurityWe have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. New-Form Tools applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information, such as retaining information in secure facilities and making personal information accessible only to authorized employees on a need-to-know basis.POLICY CHANGE:If we alter our Privacy Policy, any changes will be posted on this page of our Site so that you are always informed of the information we collect about you, how we use it and the circumstances under which we may disclose it.ACCEPTANCE OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY:By using this Site or  interactive banner ads, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy, and you adhere to the terms and conditions posted on the Site. By submitting your information, you agree that it will be governed by our Privacy Policy.
